

# RAKHEOANA LEFELA

WEB DEVELOPER

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION

Passport No: RC858180 (work visa)

Lives: Cape Town Willing to relocate: Yes

Overall web development experience: 4 year

Email: rakgew@gmail.com

Address: 20 Roseville Road, Claremont LinkedIn: @rakheoana-lefela-21a36051

Cell: +27 78 375 4146

# SKILLS

# **Coding Languages**

C#, ASP.NET JavaScript, HTML/CSS, PHP, MySQL. Typescript

#### Frameworks/Systems

MVC, React, bootstrap, Visual Studio, VScode, Git, Node.js, Microsoft SQL Server Management studio, XAMP, Azure DevOps

# EDUCATIONAL TRAINING

# Limkokwing University (Is)

Bachelor of Science: Information Technology (e-commerce)

• Enrolled from Sept. 2008 to Dec 2012

#### PROFILE

I am a web developer with 3+ years of experience and an Honors degree in information technology. I am experienced in the stages of the development life-cycle of dynamic web projects using Javascript, CSS, MySQL, .net, PHP and html.

# SOFT SKILLS

# **Coding Languages**

Teamwork.
Communication.
Yes attitude.
Service-focused.
Strong decision making.

#### HOW I SHARPEN MY SKILLS

# Codility

I love doing algorithm challenges on codility and project UELA, even though this is just a recently found hobby, it has become one of my favorite things to do.

# Udemy

From time to time I take a udemy course to learn a new skill or to gain in-depth knowledge of a language I already know.

# CAREER SUMMARY

#### **Design Guru**

Intern PHP developer | Sept 2015 - Dec 2015 Responsibilities

- Make static websites dynamic using PHP and MySOL backend.
- Modifies code to fix errors
- Build email templates.

#### **Web Traffic**

PHP deveeloper | oct. 2017 to April 2018 Responsibilities

- Plan, design and build dynamic web applications, using HTML, CSS, Javascript and PHP.
- Communicate with clients to get project requirements.

#### Lucidocean

software developer | Jun 2018 - Jan 2021 Responsibilities

- Build new features for existing projects.
- Upgrading asp.net projects UI to modern bootstrap versions.
- Administered large Data collection web applications and their database.
- Building PWA applications.

#### tools used

- AWS
- MSM queue
- IIS
- Typescript & Javascript
- asp.net
- c#
- bootstrap
- PHP
- CSS
- Insomnia & Postman
- MVC
- SVN & BitBucket

# WHAT I AM LOOKING FOR IN MY NEXT JOB

#### Roles

Web developer software Engineer web stack developer PHP developer

#### Tech

PHP

ASP.Net with Razor & JS or Blazor
.Net / .Net core Web API with Management studio
React / vue js / angular

# REFERENCES

#### LucidOcean & Solitan London

CEO.

Jonathan Crossland

Email: Jonathancrossland@gmail.com

#### **Pargo**

Web Developer, [ PHP developer @ design guru 2015]

Gevann Mullins Cell: +27789298581

Email: gevann.mullins@gmail.com

#### **Realm Digital**

Intermediate Developer Dominique Kiboku Cell: +27813516102

Email:dominiquekiboku@gmail.com



in @rakheoana-lefeLa

(alefelaR

🛭 @lefelaR

https://pedantic-pike-97968d.netlify.app/ https://ngpm.co.za/ https://ngpm.herokuapp.com/